hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah grakowski if you haven't met
yet I help coaches and course creators
grow their businesses to six seven and
eight figures and I want to help you
learn how to start find your Niche get
clients and make as much money as
possible as a coach trainer Mentor or
author now today I want to talk about
something that's a huge problem in the
coaching industry specifically and and
this is something that's on my heart
that I just want to share with you that
is it's a very kind of down-to-earth
vulnerable
unfiltered raw y'all like that I know
that so that unfiltered raw type level
teaching that I want to bring to you
today and the truth is is this is that
there's a there's so much training and
coaching out there I believe that the
coaching that you get from my
accelerator you get all my courses the
podcasts are some of the best training
that's out there for coaches and
trainers and listen if you know somebody
that's struggling in this space make
sure that you share with them this
podcast make sure that you share with
them that if they're trying to get
clients if they're trying to get people
into their business I would love to help
them this podcast is enough for
everybody to grow their business to six
figures just off the episodes of this
podcast but here's the problem that I
see a lot of people go through podcast
episodes courses they join coaching
programs and they don't do anything with
what they learn
they become addicted to learning
addicted to all the information
addicted to being told what the right
stuff is to do and asking the questions
and solving the problem see what ends up
happening mentally in our brain and God
designed us this way on purpose so we
want to just say thank you Lord I am
grateful for how you made me I am also
grateful that you have taught me that I
can make choices for myself and so you
gotta strategically choose to not do
what your brain was actually naturally
wired to do let me explain this to you
hmm your brain is wired to actually
become addicted when you learn new stuff
this helps us grow this helps us
progress our our like the the human
history y'all look at human history how
we end up growing that's the
consciousness of humanity growing and
expanding and so we all like we want to
learn we are like humans love to learn
and when it comes to stuff that we want
to learn we we love it like you guys
love listening to this podcast to learn
new things here's an unlock for you
though
don't become so addicted to learning
that you're not executing if you're
spending more time learning than
actually doing what you learn you're
going to be set up for failure
and so yes it's hard to take action on
the things that we learn
we have to kill a part of ourselves
that's nervous and worried of things not
working out not producing the result
that we want because here's the thing
learning is a safe environment nothing
bad can happen
nothing can go wrong it's all perfect
it's Utopia
when you're learning it's addictive
because it feels like Utopia you're
feeling the possibility in your life
then when you go out there to actually
execute real life slaps you in the face
and tells you you know what you don't
actually know as much as you thought you
did so then you go back and learn more
and you learn more and you learn more
when the truth is that when life slaps
you in the face and says you don't know
as much as you thought you did that's
the time to lean in
instead of going back and learning more
in in in the sense of book learning
courses podcasts and and listen I run a
business where I make money off of
people loving courses and podcasts you
get it
like like it actually
is economically not very wise for me to
make this podcast episode
because I know that will it will
actually slightly reduce the amount of
people that go through my courses but I
want that because I want people to
actually in the long term it's actually
going to increase it truthfully in the
short term it's not in the long term it
is going to increase it because I want
you to go through my trainings go
through my lessons go through my courses
Heck if you even if you're listening to
another coach another Mentor somebody
else who's out there and you're going
through their system
go through the trainings
and then apply what you learned
and then learn the next step and the
next step and the next step
you want to go learn and then do learn
and do learn and do otherwise you're
like you hit learn learn learn learn
but you still can't do past this level
and so really you've only actually
learned up to this point because
the majority of actual learning
comes by experience
comes by doing something comes by taking
action on the previous lesson
and so you gotta make your brain do
differently than what it's been
programmed to do up to this moment of
time
you have control over this
but it can be a lot harder for most of
us to do want to know why wanna know why
this is hard
I'm gonna tell you
it's trauma baby
[Music]
because at some point in our life
we took action
and did something that we learned
and we got slapped in the face so hard
that it knocked us back five to ten
years
and we don't want that to happen again
we don't want to waste so much time
doing something and then it to just
bring us right back to where we started
and so what you got to do is you gotta
go through a process of grief
or you're you're actually going to be
grieving
the future that you thought that you
should have had
the version of life that you thought you
should have had some of us are
experiencing that in our society right
now over the last four years with
covid-19 there's a version of society
that we thought would happen and it
didn't happen that way
and so now we gotta pick ourselves back
up from the collective human trauma
of the past four years
and say okay
I'm gonna actually grieve that version
of my life y'all ever watch the Loki
series on Disney
where you got the um
the the people who do the um
they they they're the time bosses or
whatever they are they're the time
managers they manage time and if it goes
too far off the timeline
there's a version of like in quantum
physics a version of history and if it
goes too far off the timeline they go
out there and they kill it they don't
allow the timeline to go past that point
okay
there's not that in real life
[Music]
now there is to a point in in like if
you there is a sort of
to a point
powers that that do stuff but not like
I'm not going to get existential on that
what happened with covid was there was a
version of our history and we literally
got knocked into a different timeline
and
I for one person was actually somebody
that that I didn't know we were gonna
get knocked into a different timeline
but I was predicting things that on our
on our current timeline if you had
talked to me back in 2017
I was talking about
the metaverse and starlink and VR right
here and if you look back in 1992 when
computers first came out there was a
book called Snow Crash by the author
Neil Stevenson and in science fiction we
actually see a sort of a future of
different timelines of humanity
that could happen especially when it's
called hard science fiction and it's
actually based off of what could happen
like the expanse on on Amazon Prime
that's called hard science fiction
you know it's not based on I mean
there's there's still stuff that's like
speculated but like a lot of it is like
okay this actually could be a future
history that we experience things like
that okay and so I had noticed that
technology most people in technology
said it's gonna take us a hundred years
to get to a certain place on the
timeline and I was telling people no
it's it's like 15 years away
y'all
I didn't know that like Kobe was gonna
happen but basically people were like
listen unless something crazy happens to
the world
literally this is I had a billionaire
tell me this is his son uh told me this
and I was like I don't want nothing
crazy to happen right like I had like I
like he's like the only way it's gonna
happen in 15 years is if something crazy
happens in the world and he told me this
in 2017.
and I'm like I don't want anything crazy
to happen like people die right
well something crazy happened covet
and it accelerated the timeline that
would have possibly been a hundred years
off in our future
to now all the same technology people
are saying what I was saying back in
2017 it's 10 years away
see five years we're now at this point
we've already gone five years from when
I made that prediction they're saying
literally Mark Zuckerberg is saying it's
10 years away Bill Gates is saying it's
10 years away Elon Musk is saying it's
10 years away
that in 10 years that we are going to
have a different world when it comes to
technology and what happened with kovid
put us on that trajectory
okay
and so knowing that
we have to make sure that we set
ourselves up for success
what ends up happening when people learn
stuff
is
they need to apply what they learn
within 12 months
or it becomes completely invalid
okay I I meet a lot of people where they
I taught courses with my mom back in
2016. okay so that was eight uh six
years ago in 2016.
they learned from my mom in 2014.
that was eight years ago
if they had applied that training within
12 months they would have made Millions
they haven't learned anything new
in eight years
and the training doesn't work anymore
the certain Concepts don't work they
have to be updated
that's why when you're in a group
coaching program like my accelerator
when you follow this podcast I keep you
up to speed with what's actually
happening in the world and I promise you
this I'm telling you 10 years the
metaverse within the next 10 years you
can get into it by buying a meta Quest 2
headset and and Oculus meta they're not
called Oculus anymore they're releasing
a new headset in October that literally
you put it on and you see the real world
around you as if it's a set of goggles
so you put the headset on but the world
around you looks the same you still see
your TV in the corner there and your
couch and it's in high resolution and
then you have the screen in front of you
where you can actually do stuff this is
literally coming out in the next 45 days
from the time of recording this podcast
they have demo videos where you can
watch it right now
okay
and so we need to make sure that what
we're learning that we apply
in the next 12 months
and that if we haven't learned something
new in the last 12 months that we
refresh our skill set
every 12 months now here's where people
get stuck
all they ever do is just keep refreshing
their skill set every 12 months but they
haven't taken action
and so they're going based off of
information
from this first time right here and what
happens is when you learn something for
the first time the human brain ends up
thinking okay that's how it's always
going to be until you apply it until you
actually experience what works and what
doesn't it's very hard to tell that's
why in our business we're still actively
building and growing coaching businesses
to six and seven figures we're working
with clients to come up with what
actually produces results
okay and so
by learning this stuff by me coaching
people on this stuff by you joining my
client growth accelerator you're able to
actually get ahead of the Curve
ahead of where everybody else is on this
journey and set yourself up for success
for consistency okay
and I'm actually hosting a live event
here you can check it out over at my
website this week about building your
own six-figure coaching business if
you're somebody that wants to build your
own six figure coaching business this is
an event that you can find the
information at my website
jeremicorkowski.com we're going to spend
five days together going over all the
stuff that you need to figure out if
you're listening to this later after the
time of this recording we're probably
still doing events like this and so be
sure to check out my website if there's
an active one and get into it and start
learning what's actually working right
now this year in the coaching business
okay
instead of you just learning new stuff
all the time
I want you to start taking what you
learned
and applying it
implementing what you learned
I need you to not be
addicted to learning and allergic to
execution
this is where most people are in their
coaching and course business
is that they're addicted to learning
and they're allergic to actually doing
what they learn
and what it takes to actually do that
is self
-discipline
and self-discipline is one of those
words that maybe we think is a bad word
is a naughty word we don't want to talk
about it we don't want to say that it's
a part of things we're looking for the
next motivation so motivation is just
it's a chemicals rising up in your body
that gets you really excited about stuff
that's what happens when you're learning
new things
but that's gonna die down so that's why
a lot of people are really addicted to
those motivation chemicals inside of
them and they're looking for their next
Motivation by learning a whole bunch of
new information but they're not applying
what they learned because they lack the
self-discipline and accountability in
their life to do so and so here's two
things that are very important that you
must do
actually three things
three things
to solve this and to actually make six
and seven and eight figures in your
business
you must have
self-discipline
I don't think I spelled that right
that's okay
you must also take
personal
responsibility
[Music]
you must take ownership
of everything in your life
for where you're at
and stop blaming
anything outside of you for why you
don't have self-discipline
and this is the hard part that most
people never get to
because they actually have to go through
this part of the journey
to succeed
you also actually there's four pieces
you have you also must have
humility
about your ability
to hold yourself accountable
you must be honest and real and take
personal responsibility for the fact
that you haven't been doing what you're
doing and that you need help with
self-discipline and there's things that
you don't know how to do and that's okay
it's perfectly okay to not know how to
do something as a business owner because
all you got to do is just find somebody
else that does
and ask them for help
in this business in the coaching
business
the people that are the most successful
love helping the people that are not
successful
it's part of the business
and so don't think that you're wasting
their time or you're bothering them by
doing that for me personally I love when
people message me and ask for help about
where they're stuck in their coaching
business or they post in the comments
because I'm able to bring the answers
that they're needing from my experience
and help raise them up to that level and
and for me it it helps in my business
since I've actually built my business
around coaching and holding other
coaches accountable and helping them
build their business successfully that
it actually helps me validate my system
it actually helps me have case study
right if I if I help a client make a
million dollars in one month in their
business
and they started from zero like my
client Rick Pino
if I help a client make eighty thousand
dollars a month in their business and
they started from zero a year ago like
my client Joshua Giles
if I help a client make 35 000 a month
in their coaching business and they were
struggling for six years and after a
year of working with me like my client
Dawn
are actually making that thirty five
thousand a month
that builds credibility that builds
trust that builds hope for the clients
that we work with for the clients that
we help for the people that we are
actually in the weeds with every single
day those that are in my accelerator
those that are my one-on-one coaching
clients those that are my Consulting
clients
it costs
20 000 a month
and it's probably gonna be going up
really soon to about 40 000 a month
per month
to consult with me to have me come in
and join your team and help you build
your business and that's what I'm
getting paid right now by my Consulting
clients
we have a very high six-figure monthly
income that we're making off of
Consulting and coaching
twenty thousand dollars a month to work
with me and do that what do you get with
that I write your copy and I run your
ads and then I help your team with the
with everything else
that's it
and when you learn how to write copy and
run ads
you can command that type of a fee you
can command that type of a fee Dan
Kennedy commands over 200 I think 200
000 per sales page that he writes plus a
commission on the results it produces
okay
and so copywriting is one of the number
one skills that you can learn and
leverage because if I write one sales
page that generates a client a million
dollars
you think it was worth it to them to pay
me 20K to do that
heck yeah
I mean where can you get that kind of
Roi most people can't and that's why
they hire me to work with them
and if they're not at that level it's
it's five thousand dollars a month to
coach with me when I won you get two
hours with me each session is 2500 bucks
for an hour
to work with me over zoom and I'm
working with you to help you build your
business and craft your messaging and
build your funnels
for the people that they're just not at
that level yet that's what the
accelerator's for
right now it's two thousand dollars to
jump into it per year and you can
actually pay monthly 12 payments on that
which is awesome it's under 170 bucks a
month for most people that's an absolute
steal that's an absolute deal of what
they're getting they get all my courses
they get coaching with me they get
trainings they get they get hot seat
copy reviews there's a copywriting day
that we have they get access to some of
our events they get discounts on select
things and they're the ones that are
building their business and growing and
listen if you're a coach if you're a
trainer if you're a mentor and you're
saying hey I need help to get clients I
need help to grow my business
jump into one of our events
jump into one of our trainings go
through this podcast jump into the
client growth accelerator join the
waiting list on the page join the
waiting list over at my website at
jeremiahkrowski.com forward slash
accelerator to be able to join next time
we open the doors to that
and what I will do is I will actually
help you
by you taking personal responsibility
by you taking self-discipline
by you holding yourself accountable by
you having the humility to ask for help
to join a program with somebody that
knows how to do it that has a proven
track record and can help hold your hand
all the way through the process
You're Now setting yourself up in an
elite category of the top one percent of
coaches that are out there
because you're saying Jeremiah I need
you to show me what I don't know I need
to be coached I need to be held
accountable I need to develop the
self-discipline that I don't have right
now to help me get more results in my
business
or you can choose to keep doing what
you're doing
keep struggling
keep
being overwhelmed keep
being upset that things aren't working
out
keep
going through courses and never doing
anything with them
keep
spending money on coaching programs and
and wasting time
when you don't have time to waste to do
that the choice is yours it really is
are you going to be
addicted to learning
but allergic to execution
or are you going to choose
that I'm going to make a small
investment into my future
one of my free events it's an investment
of just an hour of your time for five
days and you got a week to watch those
recordings and you can usually buy the
recordings afterwards
just by you
saying okay I'm gonna I'm gonna I'm
gonna give up five hours of my time if
you're making a hundred bucks an hour
that's 500 bucks
if you're making 30 bucks an hour that's
150 bucks
um think of it in terms of how much do
you make per hour
and is it worth that much to you to
actually accelerate yourself on your
journey
or do you want to keep staying where
you've been at do you want to keep
struggling to move forward with your
life and with your business
I think the latter is a much better
decision
and that's what most of the people that
have jumped into our programs the people
that have coached with me the people
that work with me the people that are
getting results in their business are
experiencing
and so I'd love to help you I'd love to
work with you if you're somebody that
wants to build a coaching business to
seven figures build a coaching business
to six figures even make just an extra
two thousand to five thousand dollars a
month
I want to help you get there
I can't wait to see you in one of my
future events that we're doing I can't
wait to walk with you through this
process so that instead of you just
trying to figure out what to do next in
your business
you actually have an action plan that
you can take to get results
all right everybody
thank you so much for being here if
you've enjoyed this podcast episode
again we got over a hundred and 79
episode or almost 180 episodes of this
podcast this is episode 180 right here
that's right
I'm pre-recording it a couple weeks in
advance so I'm having to like remember
you know
go through the podcast
each episode is about 30 minutes long
go read through some of the titles on
the podcast on Spotify or on Apple
find the episodes that you're like okay
that title really matters to me that's
exactly what I'm looking for for help
and go through those and listen through
some of those episodes
I promise you that your thinking is
going to change for the better and your
life will be improved by listening to
this podcast
that you will be able to get into an
atmosphere you know we become this the
sum total of the five people that we
spend the most time around
did you know that you can hack that
by the people that you listen to in
podcasts
so if you want to learn from somebody
that is an eight-figure coaching
business Builder
spend some time around somebody that is
listen through my podcast and you'll
grab onto just by listening some
strategies some tools some ways for you
to grow your business just by hearing
how I'm doing it on this podcast
listen I believe in you and I know that
you can succeed I know that you can do
the impossible don't ever question your
greatness don't ever question if you're
good enough don't ever wonder can I do
this there are people out there that are
less skilled less qualified and are not
producing nearly as good of stuff that
you are
that are making millions coaching and
making courses
why not you
don't let yourself be Your Own Worst
Enemy
don't let
blaming other people
and it's just my personality to not
really schedule things and the need to
be right and know the answer all the
time and never asking for help keep you
stuck
the people that make the most amount of
money have these three skill sets and
the brokest people that I know don't
just by you choosing to take personal
responsibility self-discipline and
realize I need help I need to learn some
things that I don't know and I need to
start asking a mentor to hold me
accountable you elevate your status into
the top one percent of people in the
world
in 2022
literally
yeah you do
if you just go by income
over 17 percent of the world makes over
six figures
but not 17 of everybody does this
you will be able to make six figures
faster just with what you know right now
by doing these three things
or you can keep living your life how you
have been listen I feel like if you're
listening to this part of this podcast
you've gotten this far into it
I think you're somebody that knows that
you're made for more you know that
you're made for greatness you know that
God's called you to something greater
than what you've been experiencing up to
this moment in time
it's time to stop waiting it's time to
stop wondering am I doing things the
right way am I on the right track and
it's time to start growing your business
choosing to do things that you know are
going to make your life better and step
into the future that is possible for you
there's a future timeline that has you
as a millionaire in it
are you going to choose to follow the
path that stays broke are you going to
stay on the timeline that's going to
make you a multi-millionaire the choice
is yours you can actually hop timelines
I've actually done this
I played around with it for a little
while it's not very fun once you're
going between
um
wealthy and broke and I actually went a
little too far and hopped into the broke
one and got knocked back for years
because there were lessons that I hadn't
learned from the wealthy category
and I got knocked back by four years and
had to retake the same lessons to get
back on the timeline I had to go back to
the start
sometimes that happens sometimes you've
been trying for things over and over
again and you get knocked back on your
timeline four years
we gotta go back to the beginning
don't let your fear and worry keep you
from going to that next place because
that's where your trauma was that's
where your fear was that's where your
pain was that's where everything that's
inside of you that really hurt was
remember I said I got knocked back four
years ago four and a half years ago
I am now ahead of where I was four years
ago
and I'm in a new timeline that I will
never go back to the one I was at I had
to change my friends I had to change who
I was talking to I had to stop listening
to the same music that I was listening
to I had to stop hanging out with
certain people I had to stop watching
certain things on TV I had to stop
hanging out in certain Facebook groups I
had to stop listening to certain things
that I was listening to every single day
and change where I put my focus one of
the biggest focuses that I changed as I
actually put my focus on what does God
say about me more than anything else
what is the truth that God says about me
what is the truth about how he made me
what is the truth about how I was born
and the greatness that he put inside me
and I stopped saying you know what
I'm afraid of being successful
I'm afraid of making seven figures
I'm afraid of doing what God called me
to do
and everything in our life has changed
our income has gone up our relationships
have gotten better God has restored
relationships God has brought us into a
new season of a new future of our family
and we got a new baby boy on the way
foreign
and I knew that that was our future
I knew that that was our destiny
four and a half years ago
but I didn't know how to get there and
the only way that I got there is I
humbled myself and said what don't I
know
what do I need to learn I got mentors I
got coaches I got people around me that
spoke into my life truth I got rid of
some crazy stupid idiots literally I'm
gonna be honest about that and I'm not
ashamed of calling them that that I was
listening to that were giving me advice
and I stopped listening to their advice
they got angry they got mad that I
stopped listening to them but I got
people that were ahead of me
I only took advice from people that were
making over 10 million dollars
I'm like if you're not making over 10
million I I ain't taking your advice
nope
now I'm at the point if you're not
making
over 50 million
if it comes to business I don't need
that
now sure I can learn lessons from people
that are at different levels of course
don't be so prideful that you think that
you can't learn something I there's a
billionaire that I know that he comes to
me with questions about stuff about
topics that he doesn't know
but maybe there's some people in your
life that are giving you advice that
were from your previous season that were
familiar to you
that felt good to hang out with and now
they don't really really feel very good
and they make you feel kind of anxious
every time you take their advice
it might be time to limit the amount of
exposure you have to those people and
and stop asking them for advice I've had
to do that the people that I went to
three years ago two years ago for advice
I don't go to anymore
[Music]
I don't ask them what I should do next
because they're going to take me back to
where I was
see what I'm saying
and so
when you go into a new season when you
step into a new timeline you got to get
new mentors
you gotta get new people that can run
with you to the next level
now if you're like me you might feel
like you're in a Valley season where
there's no mentors
you want to know what I found in that
season
that it was just me and holy spirit as
the mentor
that inside of me actually knew what I
needed to do I just wasn't doing it
because I had learned it in the previous
season
and now I'm getting the place where
there's new lessons that I learned going
to new levels
people say new level new Devil no I say
new level new blessing new mentors
new wisdom
to guide you
from where you've been through to where
you're going to
instead of wondering am I on the right
path you can actually do things in your
life to ensure that you're going in the
right direction
and that starts by having mentors
accountability self-discipline humility
and personal responsibility
are you gonna keep going around this
mountain again and again and again
are you going to do something different
choice is yours
all right everybody
listen if you like this episode share it
with somebody I can't wait to see you
succeed I would love to help you
let's connect we'll talk soon everybody
grow your life have a good one